// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Travelling salesman problem is an example of",
    answer: "Greedy Algorithm",
    options: [
      "Dynamic Algorithm",
      "Greedy Algorithm",
      "Recursive Approach",
      "Divide and Conquer"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The complexity of Fibonacci series is",
    answer: "O(2n)",
    options: [
      "O(log n)",
      "O(n2)",
      "O(n log n)",
      "O(2n)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is not a stable sorting algorithm?",
    answer: "Selection sort",
    options: [
      "Selection sort",
      "Insertion sort",
      "Bubble sort",
      "Merge sort"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is not a Characteristics of a Data Structure?",
    answer: "Completeness",
    options: [
      "Correctness",
      "Completeness",
      "Time Complexity",
      "Space Complexity"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "O(1) means computing time is __________________",
    answer: "Constant",
    options: [
      "Quadratic",
      "Linear",
      "Cubic",
      "Constant"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the type of the algorithm used in solving the 8 Queens problem?",
    answer: "Backtracking",
    options: [
      "Backtracking",
      "Dynamic",
      "Branch and Bound",
      "Both A and B"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The Omega notation is the formal way to express the __________ of an algorithms running time.",
    answer: "lower bound",
    options: [
      "upper bound",
      "medium bound",
      "lower bound",
      "both the lower bound and the upper bound"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Linked lists are not suitable to for the implementation of?",
    answer: "Binary search",
    options: [
      "Insertion sort",
      "Radix sort",
      "Binary search",
      "Polynomial manipulation"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In circular linked list, insertion of node requires modification of?_",
    answer: "Two pointer",
    options: [
      "One pointer",
      "Two pointer",
      "Three pointer",
      "None"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The complexity of Binary search algorithm is",
    answer: "O(log n)",
    options: [
      "O(n)",
      "O(log n)",
      "O(n2)",
      "O(n log n)"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];